Exit Art "Reactions" exhibit collection
Prints & Photographs Division, Library of Congress
- Burkhart, Kathe
  - WTC Haikus, pencil and text on paper; 0282; 1069; A 10 stanza poem imposed over a drawing of the twin towers
- Burrough, Xtine
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0283; 1951; Small faces/eyes
- Burton, Nicole
  - This is Terrorism, 0284; 2178
- Burwell III, Charles Wm.
  - Omen, 0285; 866
- Burysevicz, Mathieu
  - [Untitled], 0286; 1223
- Burysevicz, Mathieu
  - [Untitled], 0287; 1224
- Burysevicz, Mathieu
  - [Untitled], 0288; 1225
- Bush, Lawrence
  - Kaddish (Mourning Prayer), 0289; 1344; NYC skyline w/kaddish
- Bush, Lawrence
  - Menorah, 0290; 1345; Menorah w/firefighters
- Butler, Jack
  - [Untitled], 0291; 491; Fatemap and heads
- Butler, Ken
  - [Untitled], 0291b; 532; Martin Luther King quote
- Butler, Shiela
  - [Untitled], 0292; 391; "The miners canary"
- Buxton, Garrison
  - Insert planes here?, comp. art; 0292b; 3225
- Butula, Sandra
  - Uy!!, color print of painting; 0292c; 3276
- Buzzeo, Helaina
  - Week Passed 9/11, poem; 0293; 2147; Smiling faces of people who...
- Amnesty International c/o Sue Ronald
  - [Untitled], 0294; 3062; Via email: begins with "From Afghanistan to Zimbabwe countless victims are denied the protection of their basic human rights"
- Carrallas, Barbara
  - The Flag Project, 0295; 3050; I began an art = life performance...
- Caeiro, Mario
  - [Untitled], 0296; 2183
- Cahill, Anne Marie
  - Sky, 0298; 1164
- Calouski, Y.
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0300; 1380; Collage of text and images; the onion is in the center
- Cambre, Javier
  - [Untitled], comp. printout; 0300b; 3237
- Cameron, Donna
  - [Untitled], artwork & text; 0301; 71; Via mail
- Cameron, Louis
  - Riddim Warfare #1, collage; 0302; 940
- Campbell, Naomi
  - [Untitled], color copy; 0302b; 3259
- Canales, Duben
  - Jihad vs. Yeehaw, drawing on paper; 0303; 1487; Drawing of a cowboy fighting Osama Bin Laden, faxed by Anne Rowland
- Cannata, Alfredo
  - [Untitled], 0304; 1919; Black man in front of cross
- Capello, Linda
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0306; 614; Animals and buildings
- Capello, Linda
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0307; 612; Flag, landscape 3 of 3
- Caplan, Sandra
  - Downtown, watercolor on paper; 0308; 890
- Caravella, Nicole
  - [Untitled], 0309; 1618; Flag w/writing
- Carlene
  - [Untitled], 0310; 321; "Ashes to ashes..." with photo of child
- Carlinville High School/Paul Barnstable
  - [Untitled], watercolor and pen on paper; 0310b; 1272
- Carlinville High School/Sarah Black
  - [Untitled], collage; 0310c; 1273
- Carlinville High School/Kelli Trump
  - [Untitled], collage; 0310d; 1274
- Carlinville High School/Andrew T. Bloomer
  - Freedom is Not Free, crayon on paper; 0310e; 1275
- Carlinville High School/Corrine Spencer
  - [Untitled], black charcoal on paper; 0310f; 1277
- Carlinville High School/Benjamin Dreyer
  - [Untitled], 0310g; 1278
- Carlinville High School/Asghari Hamed
  - United We Stand, colored pencil on paper; 0310h; 1279
- Carlinville High School/Chuck Winsel
  - Don't Tread on Us, paint on paper; 0310i; 1281
- Carlinville High School/Cody J. Branson
  - USAF BAF, crayon on paper; 0310j; 1282
- Carlinville High School/Ashley Costello
  - [Untitled], paint on paper; 0310k; 1283
- Carlinville High School/Marcus M. Davis
  - US Marines, crayon on paper; 0310l; 1284
- Carlinville High School/Corey Fairfield
  - Grounded, paint on paper; 0310m; 1285
- Carlinville High School/Missy Scherer
  - U.S. Pride, collage; 0310n; 1286
- Carlinville High School/Kent Michaels
  - [Untitled], pen on paper; 0310o; 1289
- Carlinville High School/Clay Schmitt
  - United we stand, digital image; 0310p; 1290
- Carlinville High School/Brad Wieties
  - [Untitled], photo montage; 0310q; 1291
- Carlinville High School/Jessica Shaw
  - United We Stand, paint on paper; 0310r; 1292
- Carlinville High School/Zach Allen
  - [Untitled], 0310s; 1294
- Carlinville High School/Katie Sitter
  - USA Unites, painting on paper; 0310t; 1295
- Carlsson, Gabriella
  - [Untitled], 0311; 2000; Glued to the tv set
- Carlyle, Virginia
  - [Untitled], 0312; 293; "Eye of the Storm"
- Carpenter, Jason
  - life in LA is normal, text; 0312b; 3218
- Carpeter, Victoria A.
  - [Untitled], gouache and ink; 0313; 865; Lighting bolt
- Carr, Kim
  - [Untitled], graphite on tracing paper; 0314; 836; Drawing of figure lying on the ground in lower right hand corner
- Carter, Michael
  - Masque of White Death, poem; 0315; 2153
- Caruso, Hwa Young
  - [Untitled], 0316; 3023; Via email
- Casey, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0317; 2206; Going to California 1 of 3
- Casey, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0318; 2207; Kiosk 2 of 3
- Casey, Elizabeth
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0319; 2208; Flag and hand 3 of 3
- Castagna, Elizabeth
  - Between, charcoal, acrylic, polymer emulsion on canvas; 0320; 1877; Text and art
- Castagna, Elizabeth
  - Afterthought, 0321; 1878; Poems after 1-11
- Castaignet, Michel
  - [Untitled], 0322; 2073
- Castria, Jimena
  - Obsessed?, collage; 0323; 1242
- Castrucci, Andrew
  - U.S.A. R.I.P., pencil on paper; 0324; 1080; Text "U.S.A. R.I.P." handwritten in pencil
- Catania, Mimmo
  - [Untitled], 0325; 2120; I told Muriel
- Cavanagh, Henry
  - [Untitled], ink and text on paper; 0326; 1062; Juxtaposition of typed text from Exit Art and hiw own written text in reaction
- Cecere, Jennifer
  - [Untitled], 0327; 1245; Diamonds
- Celin, Mauro
  - [Untitled], printout; 0328; 1825; Fireman with gas mask
- Cerrito, Chandra
  - New Fears #5, drawing; 0329; 629; Shadow pane
- Chabot, Pamela
  - [Untitled], 0331; 2124; To Whom This May Concern...
- Chaile, Julio
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0332; 101; Via mail
- Chaldakov, Nick
  - Stop of Death, 0333; 603; Hand
- Chaldakov, Nick
  - [Untitled], 0334; 602; Brick wall kiss
- Chan, Ed
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0335; 843; Photograph of man hold sign which says "Arrest Giuliani"
- Chan, Kristina Marita
  - [Untitled], 0336; 1202; Stars and ny times
- Chansky, Matt
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0337; 88; By mail
- Charles, Ms. J.
  - [Untitled], 0338; 2192; Jump
- Chase, Colin
  - Words Fail, 0339; 3077
- Chauhan, Sumita
  - Not A Choice Of Life...Not A Choice Of Death..., lino print; 0340; 1999; 4 figures
- Cheddar, Tillamook
  - WTC Tribute III, 0342; 489; Dog art
- Chen, Howie
  - Remembering the weather that day, inkjet print; 0343; 1549; Weather charts
- Chen, Mary
  - [Untitled], 0344; 2174; All I can say is, It's said
- Chen, Shiau-Peng
  - [Untitled], 0345; 174; E-mailed image
- Chen Lin, Chia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0346; 334; 1 of 3
- Chen Lin, Chia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0347; 335; 2 of 3
- Chen Lin, Chia
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0348; 336; 3 of 3
- Chepelyk, Oksana
  - [Untitled], 0350; 2041; New order
- Chepelyk, Oksana
  - [Untitled], 0351; 2042; New order and girl
- Chermayeff, Sasha
  - [Untitled], poem; 0352; 3079; Death...
- Chermamayeff, Sasha
  - [Untitled], poem; 0353; 3080; In birth...
- Chermayeff, Sasha
  - [Untitled], poem; 0354; 3060; Death is the creation
- Chernikowski, Stephanie
  - Unreal City, poetry and photo; 0355; 968
- Child, Abigail
  - [Untitled], 0356; 11; Tower of Babel and WTC tower remnants
- Chilindron, Marta
  - [Untitled], clear vinyl; 0357; 1018; Image of NYC skyline with twin towers
- Chin, Daryl
  - [Untitled], 0358; 389; "Because my gout..."
- Chong, Cecil
  - Dialogue/September 10 & September 12, photos of paintings; 0359; 961
- Christakos, Yiannis
  - [Untitled], 0360; 405; Squiggle drawing
- Christgau, Robert
  - Robert Christgau: Two Playlists, 0361; 734
- Christian, Anton
  - Can You Imagine Peace Without Fairness, 0362; 1935; Arafat
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0363; 2209; Large US mail 1 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0364; 2210; Various people walking US mail 2 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0365; 2211; Security 3 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0366; 2212; Military with flag 4 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0367; 2213; Various military, other people 5 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0368; 2214; Various characters with mail 6 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0369; 2215; A hard look at irony 7 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0370; 2216; Postman and military 8 of 9
- Christian, Russel
  - [Untitled], 0371; 2217; Plane and fireman 9 of 9
- Christie, Allison
  - [Untitled], 0372; 360; Email page
- Christiner, Hedina
  - Piece of Peace, 0373; 247; "A," rabbit
- Chunn, Nancy
  - [Untitled], 0374; 1419; NY Times frontpage headline from September 12.
- Church, Eileen
  - [Untitled], 0375; 3100
- Churko, Catherine
  - Oh My People, text and drawing; 0376; 1771; WTC
- Chutiwongpeti, Sarawut
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0378; 118; Via email
- Chwatsky, Ann
  - [Untitled], 0379; 896; 1 of 2 photo
- Chwatsky, Ann
  - [Untitled], 0380; 897; 2 of 2 photo
- Cilek, Toni
  - [Untitled], 0381; 898
- Cina, Alex
  - [Untitled], drawing on construction paper; 0382; 2298
- Cina, Isabella
  - [Untitled], drawing on construction paper; 0383; 2297
- Cina, Sara
  - [Untitled], drawing on construction paper; 0384; 2296
- Cina, Tucker
  - [Untitled], drawing on construction paper; 0385; 2299
- Cinader, Martha J.
  - [Untitled], 0386; 37; Poem via email
- Cinder, Elizabeth
  - Aftermath, 0387; 852; Bambi
- Citrin, Maggie
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0388; 347
- Clancy, Jeremiah
  - Untitled, 2001, 0390; 111
- Clark, Ursula
  - Peace/Bombs (after war there's peace?), mixed media; 0391; 1433; Abstract design composed of two vertical columns of squares and dots
- Clarke Mendes, Cybele C.
  - [Untitled], photo; 0392; 619; Picnic
- Clary, Braden
  - [Untitled], 0393; 1057; Jupiter
- Clements, Mike
  - [Untitled], 0394; 3003
- Cliffe, B.
  - [Untitled], crayon and ink on paper; 0395; 835; Drawing of three children reciting the pledge of allegiance with word bubbles
- Cloutier, Chris
  - Rethink, water color on paper; 0396; 2234
- Clovis, Donna
  - [Untitled], photo; 0397; 656; Love one another - goes with text # 715. 1 of 2
- Cobb, Josy
  - [Untitled], collage; 0399; 669
- Cobbs, P. J.
  - Peace?, mixed media; 0400; 1847; Dark cube with white border
- Coffin, Chris
  - [Untitled], 0401; 933; Everyone...
- Cohen, Guy
  - The Writing on the Wall (6/01-?), 0402; 1261; Photo of artwork in frame; a female face in center
- Cohen, Jem
  - Both want war, both unelected, digital image with text; 0403; 1022; In collaboration with Kim Maley of "Pretty." Made as a sticker, poster, and flyer of this size. Image of Osama Bin Laden and George Bush side by side with the words "Both Want War, Both Unelected"
- Cohen, Nancy
  - [Untitled], collage of burnt and handmade paper; 0404; 1047; 1 of 2
- Cohen, Nancy
  - [Untitled], salt on handmade paper; 0405; 1048; 2 of 2
- Cohen, Nancy
  - [Untitled], 0406; 1041; Lantern
- Cohen, Natasha
  - [Untitled], digital copy of polaroid transfer emulsion print; 0407; 867
- Cohen, Rose E.
  - We Wait Too Long, text on paper; 0408; 1602; 11 stanza poem on paper
- Colbourne, Erik
  - The World Trade Center attack was awful and my cousin's leg got broken from the people running on him..., drawing; 0410; 555; 5 of 16
- Cole, Kenny
  - [Untitled], 0411; 402; "Respond Today"
- Cole, Norma
  - The Catastrophe, 0412; 611; Poem; try to hang side by side with #610
- Cole, Rachael
  - "August 2001", drawing; 0413; 1337
- Coleman, Anna Mosby
  - Transcription, text; 0413b; 3229
- Coleman, Ellen
  - Tight, print on paper; 0414; 1120
- Collery, Paula
  - [Untitled], photo image and paint; 0415; 1547; Face in sky
- Coltrain, Justin Najee
  - [Untitled], 0416; 549; 10 of 16
- Conger, Rob
  - [Untitled], 0419; 1593; Digital face
- Conger, Rob
  - [Untitled], 0420; 1592; Digital face
- Conger, Rob
  - [Untitled], 0421; 1591; Numbers and layered text
- Connolly, Jane
  - [Untitled], 0422; 1207; Loving is a healer
- Connolly, Joe and Cathy
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0423; 815; Photograph of a painting by Patti Tronolone
- Conrad, Denise
  - [Untitled], 0424; 740
- Cook, Brenda
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0425; 1411; The word "savior" on a dark background
- Cook, Kristen
  - A Dark View, 0427; 1759; In slow tones,
- Cooley, Mark
  - [Untitled], 0428; 1110; Paper airplane
- Coon, Mimi
  - # 186, 0429; 1031; Firey square 1 of 2
- Crow, Cheryl
  - [Untitled], 0430; 1341; 911
- Coon, Mimi
  - # 187, 0430b; 1032; Square 2 of 2
- Cooper, Mark
  - A Piece For Peace, photo; 0431; 48; Via mail
- Cords, Annette
  - I'll be your mirror, 0432; 1186
- Corman, Gene
  - Our Country and Our President, 0433; 827; Herman, a political cartoon by Jim Unger
- Corr, William Hanbury
  - [Untitled], 0434; 588; Burnt holey paper
- Corrigan, Mariah
  - [Untitled], color print; 0434b; 3266
- Cortez, Diego
  - Smart Weapons?, 0435; 186; Prose, "Smart Weapons?"
- Costanzo, Jim
  - Our grief is not a cry for war, photograph (digital print); 0437; 1624
- Cotrim, Celia Almeida
  - Where Am I? What Time Is It, computer print out; 0438; 956
- Covre, Roberto
  - emoticon 11.9.2001, 0440; 119
- Cowell, David
  - Into the Unknown, digital painting; 0441; 3202
- Cox, Stephen W.
  - [Untitled], drawing; 0442; 142; (Squiggle)
- Crampton, Nancy
  - Grid; skewed & muted, acrylic on papercut; 0444; 1641; Swirly abstract
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0445; 1801; 1801-1809; they're there
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0446; 1802; 1801-1809; American Red Cross
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0447; 1803; 1801-1809; star chart
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0448; 1804; 1801-1809; darkened text
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0449; 1805; 1801-1809; grate
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0450; 1806; 1801-1809; big text
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0451; 1807; 1801-1809; to the people of NY
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0452; 1808; 1801-1809; statue of liberty
- Cray, Fred
  - Missing Persons, 0453; 1809; 1801-1809; a nation challenged
- Cronin, Margaret
  - In The Light Of Absence / Reclaim The Sky, poem; 0454; 2146; 2 poems
- Cross, Tania
  - [Untitled], photograph; 0455; 2048; Photo of sun shining through leaves
- Crowe, Nick
  - Financial Times, 29 December 2001, 0457; 1060; Newspaper
- Crowley, Ana
  - [Untitled], 0458; 499; Triangle
- Cruickshank-Hagenbuckle, Geoffrey
  - Perfect Vision Beyond the Grave And a Hell of a Lot of Yelling, poem; 0459; 2148; Perfect vision...
- Cruise, Wilma
  - [Untitled], 0460; 2144
- Cruz, Eileen
  - [Untitled], collage; 0461; 704
- Cruz-Castro, Pedro E.
  - [Untitled], 0462; 270; Map with profiles of bodies
- Cubillos, Frank
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0463; 2094; Angel figure in center w/flowers above head and the word "hope" in center
- Cubit, Carla
  - [Untitled], digital photo; 0464; 828; "Babylon has fallen" photo of barbie on can
- Cui, Ning Ning
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0465; 790; Mailed from: Shandong Academy of Fine Arts Jinan, Shandong, P.R. China
- Cukier, Jose
  - Transformer, painting; 0466; 2082
- Culbert, Tara & Stuart Solzberg
  - [Untitled], 0467; 505; Milk bottle with figures
- Culbertson, Janet
  - [Untitled], 0468; 309; Outline of plane painting
- Culture & Conflict group
  - Back and Front Cover, 0469; 1125; Simon says
- Cummings, Patricia
  - [Untitled], digital image; 0470; 1616; "in a sudden moment"
- Cummings, Patricia
  - [Untitled], 0471; 1818; Letter: when in the course of human events"
- Cummings, Patricia
  - Under God, 0472; 1819; Hand over script text
- Cunningham, Linda
  - [Untitled], 0474; 938; Collaboration Linda Cunningham and Sarah White
- Cunningham, Linny Morris
  - Studies for Series: WTC 6-10-78: 9-11-01, photographs; 0475; 2256; 1 of 4
- Cunningham, Linny Morris
  - Studies for Series: WTC 6-10-78: 9-11-01, 0476; 2257; 2 of 4
- Cunningham, Linny Morris
  - Studies for Series: WTC 6-10-78: 9-11-01, 0477; 2258; 3 of 4
- Cunningham, Linny Morris
  - Studies for Series: WTC 6-10-78: 9-11-01, 0478; 2259; 4 of 4
- Cunningham, Trisha K.
  - [Untitled], inkjet print on paper; 0479; 1028; Image of blue sky with large white cloud
- Cyphers, Peggy
  - [Untitled], 0480; 1633; Musical score on the left side on the page, vertical. Moth along the bottom and right side
- Czerkies, Pete
  - From Peace to Anger, 0481; 2038; Broken hand
- D
  - Dream State 10:05 a.m., 9/11/01, photograph (digital print); 0482; 675; Photo of people looking at WTC smoking.
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], pen on paper; 0483a; 877; Skull - two pages of text and drawings in pen
- Anonymous
  - [Untitled], pen on paper; 0483b; 877; Skull - two pages of text and drawings in pen
- D'Amato, Arlette Barbosa
  - Upside Down, crayon on paper; 0486; 844
- D'Aquino, Jason
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0488; 115; Via mail
- Dahl, Ronald
  - [Untitled], 0489; 2280; Whirls trade off...
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0490; 1710; Image of police and fire department badges collaged over stock market indexes. "The Bill Has Been Paid" written across the top left
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0491; 1711; Image of interior with "he says humor isn't dead just people and then there's a sudden halt & he falls off the page" written top left
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0492; 1712; Image of text quotes with "Wall Street Journal" logo and "& Investing" in top right corner. Double image
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0493; 1713; Image of stock indexes with elephant and photographs of world leaders (Hussein, Bin Laden, Bush) behind the elephant's trunk
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0494; 1714; Image of stock index with broken apart police badge in bottom left corner and complete badge of fire department in top right corner
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0495; 1715; Image layers of text with "The Sleepwalker" written top left
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0496; 1716; Poem titled, "Putting on Airs"
- Dalachinsky, Steve
  - [Untitled], collage; 0497; 1717; Poem with "the phone call (first)" collaged top right
- Dalmose, Jesper
  - I have three wishes..., text; 0497b; 3239
- Dalton, Toni
  - Subway Angel, digital image; 0498; 1519; Subway w/angel
- Dana, Steven
  - Patriotism Starts at Home, collage on paper; 0499; 738; Young boy with a toy soldier in front of a small table
- Dana, Steven
  - Anthrax, 0500; 739; An obscured female face on right side with four children in a line on left side
- Dana, Steven
  - [Untitled], mix media; 0501; 1777; Drawings with cut-out images glued on
- Daniels, Jim
  - [Untitled], 0502; 39; Poem via mail. First line: "Okay, it's 10:17 and my daughter..."
- Dann, Robin
  - Dear Twin Towers, 0503; 3087; Dear Twin Towers,
- Dannatt, Adrian
  - [Untitled], 0504; 130; I live in Tribeca...
- Danson, Andrew
  - The Cause & Effect, 0505; 106
- Daudier, Yvee
  - [Untitled], 0506; 1472
- Dashper, Julian
  - [Untitled], text; 0506b; 3279; Julian Dashper is coming to New York
- Chen, Abre
  - Efforts to Calm the Nation's Fears, digital image; 0507; 987; Abstract exploding image with large text over it
- Fox, David
  - Won't Panic, digital image; 0508; 986; Background of crashing waves with a poem in white text over it
- Davidson
  - [Untitled], photo; 0509; 469; Doll
- Davin, Francois
  - [Untitled], 0510; 187; Prose poem, "Puzzled by the triple..."
- Davis, Debra
  - [Untitled], 0511; 268; "The body and the lens"
- Davis, Eric
  - Untitled (WTC 6), 0512; 873; Is art inadequate
- Davis, Lawrence
  - [Untitled], 0514; 1755
- Dawson, David
  - Desktop, 0515; 1231; Comp. Icons
- De Biasi, Florentina
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0516; 1470; Collage of images stapled together
- de Creeft, DM
  - [Untitled], collage; 0517; 584
- de Lannoy, Caroline
  - [Untitled], 0518; 511; Dark square
- De Rosette, Angela
  - "SP.m. 0911" 1/200 (scream), print; 0521; 202
- De Sa, Alvaro
  - [Untitled], 0522; 1929; 9 boxes w/arrows
- De Sa, Alvaro
  - [Untitled], 0523; 1930; 9 boxes w/arrows inside them
- De Sa, Alvaro
  - [Untitled], 0524; 1931; 9 boxes w/arrows and patterns
- Dean Dresser, Noreen
  - [Untitled], 0525; 1620; Secretary of Defense text
- Decker, Amy N.
  - [Untitled], 0526; 583; Drawings 1 of 4
- Decker, Amy N.
  - [Untitled], 0527; 582; Drawings 2 of 4
- Decker, Amy N.
  - [Untitled], 0528; 581; Drawings 3 of 4
- Decker, Amy N.
  - [Untitled], 0529; 580; Drawings 4 of 4
- De Coste, Patrick
  - Antigonish Boy, 0530; 368
- Dedomenici, Richard
  - Time to Rebuild, 0531; 3076
- DeFranco, Michelle
  - God Bless America, photograph; 0532; 1830; Shop Window, West Houston Street, September 13, 2001
- Del Rosario, Marianno
  - Blackout, acrylic on paper; 0533; 1639; Black sheet of paper
- Deleplanque, Nana
  - Irene, photocopy of drawing; 0535; 3067; Image of woman's face. Her head turns into a foot with its toenails painted
- Delford Brown, Robert
  - Another Map to Nevada Via Denver, digital image; 0536; 1891; Circles and Nevada
- Delgado, Willy
  - [Untitled], 0537; 1690; Flag w/United We Stand
- Delgado, Michael
  - [Untitled], 0538; 556; 4 of 16
- Dell'Antonia, Giancarlo
  - Something thin slips me from the hands, 0539; 181
- DelMonico, Mary
  - [Untitled], 0540; 1235; Exposed
- Deluca, Linda
  - [Untitled], 0541; 953; "dominate the time..."
- DeMeo, Christine
  - [Untitled], 0542; 7; Jpg and poem via email
- DeMonte, Claudia
  - [Untitled], artwork/poem; 0543; 105
- Denes, Agnes
  - Wheatfield-A Confrontation, text; 0544; 1213
- Denes, Agnes
  - Wheatfield- A Confrontation (Remembering: Wheatfield, Blue sky, 0545; 1214; WTC and wheat
- Dennis, Linda
  - After Delecroix - Attacked by a Tiger, pencil on paper; 0547; 1491; Detailed pencil drawing of a contorted woman being attacked by a beast
- Deshpande, Nivedita
  - [Untitled], 0548; 2045; Pieces of wood on black b/g
- de Stoffner
  - Bombs and Beans, 0549; 1760; Drawing of two women with the phrase "Bombs and Beans" written across
- deVallance, Brendan
  - [Untitled], 0550; 1588; "watered down..."
- DeVitis, Emilia
  - [Untitled], 0551; 942; When planes become weapons
- Di Cosola, Lois
  - [Untitled], watercolor; 0552; 916; Our tears flow together
- Dib, Lisa
  - [Untitled], 0553; 1217; "How long would we walk?"
- Dib, Lisa
  - [Untitled], 0554; 1218; "The hum underfoot..."
- Dicker, Richard & Diekest, Tom
  - Osamma Been Gardenin, 0554b; 1816; Sans music museum
- DiGia, Daniel
  - Nothing feels safe anymore, picture (digital print); 0555; 1796
- Diodato, Baldo
  - [Untitled], 0556; 1948; Olives
- Domenico, Olivero
  - [Untitled], artwork; 0558; 117; Via email www.jamcafe.com/olivero
- Donovan, William
  - [Untitled], ink stamp; 0560; 660; Coffins
- Dorell, Karni
  - Dialogue - The Beginning, digital print; 0561; 1793
- Dorfman, Elissa
  - [Untitled], 0562; 73; Artwork (watercolor)
- Dorn, John F.
  - Sept. 11, 2001, pen on paper; 0563; 748; A hand drawn sad face with teardrops coming from eye
- Dorsett, Garrick
  - [Untitled], 0564; 577; Hairy patriot
- Dorsett, Garrick
  - [Untitled], 0565; 576; Gun t-shirt
- Dorsett, Garrick
  - [Untitled], 0566; 575; Bike messenger
- Doster, Eileen
  - The Target of Your Hate, watercolor on paper; 0567; 1096; Concentric circles of varying shades with the word "hate" in the center
- Dotson, Danny
  - [Untitled], text and pencil on paper; 0568; 1074; A 2001 calendar with the months of September, October, November and December scratched out.
- Dowens, Willie
  - [Untitled], 0569; 601; Dear diary
- Doyle, Richard T.
  - Fourth of July, 1965, 0570; 2010; Poem
- Dreams, Liz
  - Don't Call Me Ground Zero, oil; 0571; 1094
- Dragoeva, Mavromatti
  - [Untitled], color print; 0571b; 3250
- Dreisorner, Jorge
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0572; 1392; Two rectangular image collages arranged vertically on page www.holycow.de
- Dreisorner, Jorge
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0573; 1391; Image collage composed of three different segments arranged vertically www.holycow.de
- Dreisorner, Jorge
  - [Untitled], mixed media; 0574; 1395; Rectangular image collage arranged vertically with a veiled woman's face in center, www.holycow.de
- Dreisorner, Jorge